The war of angels has come to earth.
The Devil Conspiracy is a horror, fantasy, science
fiction film directed by Nathan Frankowski.
A powerful biotech company has breakthrough technology allowing them to clone
history’s most influential people with just a few fragments of DNA.
Behind this company is a cabal of Satanists that steals the shroud
of Christ, putting them in possession of Jesus’ DNA.
The clone will serve as the ultimate offering to the devil.
The Archangel Michael comes to earth and will stop at
nothing to end the devil’s conspiracy.
Laura, played by Alice Orr-Ewing.
Father Marconi / Michael, played by Joe Doyle.
Liz, played by Eveline Hall.
Archangel Michael, played by Peter Mensah.
Lucifer, played by Joe Anderson.
Dr. Laurent, played by Brian Caspe.
The Devil Conspiracy is a 2022 science fiction horror film written and
produced by Ed Alan and directed by Nathan Frankowski.
It stars Alice Orr-Ewing, Joe Doyle, Eveline Hall, Peter Mensah, Joe
Anderson, Spencer Wilding, Brian Caspe and James Faulkner.
Filmed in the Czech Republic, it was released at the Brussels International Fantastic
Film Festival on September 10, 2022, and in theaters on January 13, 2023.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of jesus christ, supernatural
horror, complicated, farcical, melodramatic.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.